https://redflower.com/privacy-terms/

25%OFF $200+ JOY25, 20%OFF $125+ JOY20, 15%OFF $50+ JOY15 & FREE Shippingx
red flower privacy policy and legal notice
at red flower, inc., we are committed to protecting your privacy. this privacy policy and legal notice will advise you about how we protect your personal information, what choices you have concerning the use of that information, your legal rights as a copyright owner, and other pertinent legal information.
the information we collect and how we use it
we collect information on the site in order to make it possible for you to access all the features on our site and to enhance your overall experience on our site. you can browse our site without submitting any personally identifiable information, but we do collect some anonymous information when you access our site.
information provided by you
when you visit our site, you will be invited to provide personal information to purchase an product or subscription, or to join our mailing list. to purchase a product or subscription, you will be asked for your name, billing and shipping addresses, e-mail address, credit card number and credit card expiration date. to join our mailing list, you will be asked for your e-mail address only.
information shared with third parties
we may use your contact data to send you information about red flower. you may always opt out of receiving future mailings - see the “opt out” section below.
in addition, we may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, conducting sweepstakes and other promotional activities, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. these red flower agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. other than our outside agents and certain red flower suppliers and vendors, we keep all of your personal information private and will not share it with any third party, unless you have authorized us to or we are legally required to do so. red flower may also release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of red flower, our users, or others.
security of your informationsecurity of your information
when you purchase a product or subscription online, we need to obtain your credit card number.
in addition, we may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, conducting sweepstakes and other promotional activities, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. these red flower agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. other than our outside agents and certain red flower suppliers and vendors, we keep all of your personal information private and will not share it with any third party, unless you have authorized us to or we are legally required to do so. red flower may also release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of red flower, our users, or others.
in addition, we may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, conducting sweepstakes and other promotional activities, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. these red flower agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. other than our outside agents and certain red flower suppliers and vendors, we keep all of your personal information private and will not share it with any third party, unless you have authorized us to or we are legally required to do so. red flower may also release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of red flower, our users, or others.
in addition, we may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, conducting sweepstakes and other promotional activities, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. these red flower agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. other than our outside agents and certain red flower suppliers and vendors, we keep all of your personal information private and will not share it with any third party, unless you have authorized us to or we are legally required to do so. red flower may also release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of red flower, our users, or others.
in addition, we may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, conducting sweepstakes and other promotional activities, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. these red flower agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. other than our outside agents and certain red flower suppliers and vendors, we keep all of your personal information private and will not share it with any third party, unless you have authorized us to or we are legally required to do so. red flower may also release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of red flower, our users, or others.
copyright © 1997 - 2020 red flower, inc.
Privacy & Terms
Loading...
Subscribe
